Doll & Richards Gallery
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
- Financial Records, 1871-1973, bulk 1902-1969, Series 5:; (Boxes 18-69, 79, BV81-112; 55 linear feet)
  - Sales Records, circa 1883, 1901-1973, bulk 1902-1968, 5.2:
    - Sales and Work Order Forms (Box 67)
      - Nos. D8,300-D8,399, May 7, 1953 - January 7, 1954 (Box 67, Folder 1)
      - Nos. D8,400-D8,499, January 7 - June 2, 1954 (Box 67, Folder 2)
      - Nos. D8,500-D8,599, June 4, 1954 - January 10, 1955 (Box 67, Folder 3)
      - Nos. D8,600-D8,699, January 10 - September 8, 1955 (Box 67, Folder 4)
      - Nos. D8,700-D8,799, September 8, 1955 - April 3, 1956 (Box 67, Folder 5)
      - Nos. D8,800-D8,899, April 4 - November 23, 1956 (Box 67, Folder 6)
      - Nos. D8,900-D8,999, November 24, 1956 - April 26, 1957 (Box 67, Folder 7)
      - Nos. D9,000-D9,099, April 29, 1957 - January 22, 1958 (Box 67, Folder 8)
      - Nos. D9,100-D9,199, January 22 - June 24, 1958 (Box 67, Folder 9)
      - Nos. D9,200-D9,299, June 26, 1958 - January 14, 1959 (Box 67, Folder 10)
      - Nos. D9,300-D9,399, January 21 - August 31, 1959 (Box 67, Folder 11)
      - Nos. D9,319A-D9,378A, April 3 - July 10, 1959 (Box 67, Folder 12)
      - Nos. D9,400-D9,499, September 1, 1959 - April 28, 1960 (Box 67, Folder 13)
      - Nos. D9,500-D9,599, April 28 - November 28, 1960 (Box 67, Folder 14)
      - Nos. D9,600-D9,699, November 28, 1960 - August 9, 1961 (Box 67, Folder 15)
      - Nos. D9,628A-D9,677A, September 21 - December 2, 1961 (Box 67, Folder 16)
      - Nos. D9,700-D9,799, August 9, 1961 - April 5, 1962 (Box 67, Folder 17)
      - Nos. L1 - L99, September 10 - October 8, 1926 (Box 67, Folder 18)
      - Nos. L100 - L199, October 8 - December 1, 1926 (Box 67, Folder 19)
      - Nos. L200 - L299, October 18 - November 3, 1926; December 2, 1926 - January 11, 1927 (Box 67, Folder 20)
      - Nos. L300 - L399, November 2-29, 1926 (Box 67, Folder 21)
      - Nos. L400 - L499, November 29 - December 27, 1926 (Box 67, Folder 22)
      - Nos. L500 - L599, December 28, 1926 - January 6, 1927 (Box 67, Folder 23)
      - Nos. L600 - L699, January 7 - April 12, 1927 (Box 67, Folder 24)
      - Nos. L700 - L799, February 2-28, 1927; April 15 - June 2, 1927 (Box 67, Folder 25)
    - Sales and Work Order Forms (Box 68)
      - Nos. L800 - L899, March 2 - April 14, 1927 (Box 68, Folder 1)
      - Nos. L900 - L999, April 14 - May 24, 1927 (Box 68, Folder 2)
      - Nos. L1,000 - L1,099, May 24 - July 25, 1927 (Box 68, Folder 3)
      - Nos. L1,100 - L1,199, July 26 - October 26, 1927 (Box 68, Folder 4)
      - Nos. L1,200 - L1,299, October 27, 1927 - February 27, 1928 (Box 68, Folder 5)
      - Nos. L1,300 - L1,398, February 27 - October 2, 1928 (Box 68, Folder 6)
      - Nos. L1,400 - L1,499, October 6, 1928 - February 15, 1929 (Box 68, Folder 7)
      - Nos. L1,500 - L1,599, February 15 - September 18, 1929 (Box 68, Folder 8)
      - Nos. L1,600 - L1,699, September 20, 1929 - January 10, 1930 (Box 68, Folder 9)
      - Nos. L1,700 - L1,799, February 11 - December 6, 1930 (Box 68, Folder 10)
      - Nos. L1,800 - L1,899, December 8, 1930 - August 17, 1931 (Box 68, Folder 11)
      - Nos. L1,900 - L1,999, September 14, 1931 - May 16, 1933 (Box 68, Folder 12)
      - Nos. L2,000 - L2,099, May 16, 1933 - October 5, 1940 (Box 68, Folder 13)
      - Nos. L2,100 - L2,199, October 7, 1940 - May 19, 1941; June 3 - November 4, 1942 (Box 68, Folder 14)
      - Nos. L2,200 - L2,299, November 10, 1942 - February 19, 1943 (Box 68, Folder 15)
      - Nos. L2,300 - L2,359, February 19 - May 6, 1943 (Box 68, Folder 16)
      - Nos. L3,809, 1935, April 16 (Box 68, Folder 17)
      - Nos. LE950 - LE1,078, March 28 - November 10, 1927 (Box 68, Folder 18)
      - Nos. S10,000 - S10,099, October 31, 1902 - July 9, 1903 (Box 68, Folder 19)
      - Nos. S10,100 - S10,199, July 9 - September 2, 1903 (Box 68, Folder 20)
      - Nos. S10,200 - S10,299, September 2 - December 8, 1903 (Box 68, Folder 21)
      - Nos. S10,300 - S10,399, December 10, 1903 - July 1, 1904 (Box 68, Folder 22)
      - Nos. S10,400 - S10,499, July 1 - October 13, 1904 (Box 68, Folder 23)
      - Nos. S10,500 - S10,599, October 19, 1904 - March 21, 1905 (Box 68, Folder 24)
      - Nos. S10,600 - S10,699, March 27 - August 25, 1905 (Box 68, Folder 25)
      - Nos. S10,700 - S10,799, August 25, 1905 - March 30, 1906 (Box 68, Folder 26)
      - Nos. S10,800 - S10,899, March 30 - October 17, 1906 (Box 68, Folder 27)
      - Nos. S10,900 - S10,999, October 29, 1906 - April 27, 1907 (Box 68, Folder 28)
    - Sales and Work Order Forms (Box 69)
      - Nos. S11,000 - S11,099, April 27 - September 18, 1907 (Box 69, Folder 1)
      - Nos. S11,100 - S11,199, September 23, 1907 - January 28, 1908 (Box 69, Folder 2)
      - Nos. S11,200 - S11,299, February 10 - November 27, 1908 (Box 69, Folder 3)
      - Nos. S11,300 - S11,399, November 30, 1908 - October 5, 1909 (Box 69, Folder 4)
      - Nos. S11,400 - S11,499, October 5, 1909 - November 29, 1910 (Box 69, Folder 5)
      - Nos. S11,500 - S11,599, November 29, 1910 - November 22, 1911 (Box 69, Folder 6)
      - Nos. S11,600 - S11,699, November 22, 1911 - December 20, 1912 (Box 69, Folder 7)
      - Nos. S11,700 - S11,799, December 21, 1912 - May 11, 1914 (Box 69, Folder 8)
      - Nos. S11,800 - S11,899, August 15, 1914 - February 28, 1918 (Box 69, Folder 9)
      - Nos. S11,900 - S11,999, February 28, 1918 - August 6, 1923 (Box 69, Folder 10)
      - Nos. S12,000 - S12,063, August 15, 1923 - March 1, 1934 (Box 69, Folder 11)
      - Helen Plowden/William Stanley Haseltine, Box 1, January 9, 1950 - November 8, 1952 (Box 69, Folder 12)
      - Helen Plowden/William Stanley Haseltine, Box 2, 1952, August - 1953, October (Box 69, Folder 13)
      - Helen Plowden/William Stanley Haseltine, Box 3, 1951, November; 1954, March - 1956, February (Box 69, Folder 14)
      - Helen Plowden/William Stanley Haseltine, Box 4, October 16, 1956 - February 27, 1958 (Box 69, Folder 15)
      - Helen Plowden/William Stanley Haseltine, Box 5, 1958, March - 1961, June (Box 69, Folder 16)
      - Note Filed with Forms, circa November 25, 1960 (Box 69, Folder 17)
    - Consignment Account Statements, Letterpress Copybook #7, January 19, 1949 - May 1, 1959 (Box 79 (sol), Folder 1)
    - Consignment Account Statements, Letterpress Copybook #8, August 21, 1959 - March 10, 1967 (Box 79 (sol), Folder 2)
- Inventory Records, 1881-1969, bulk 1900s-1940s, Series 6:; (Boxes 69-70, BV113-128; 2.3 linear feet)
  Inventory records provide another access point in which to research the provenance of artwork held by Doll & Richards. There are seven volumes of ledgers which record details of artwork on hand at Doll & Richards from 1881-1969. Also found are inventory books for prints and frames, including a frame profile book that shows cross-sections of frame moldings and an index to frame manufacturers.
  Entries in the records of works on hand typically include the artist's name, title of work, description, cost, date received, remarks, owner, price, and disposition. Each volume contains separate indices for artists and for owners. Identification numbers are assigned to each entry. Each volume has been assigned specific page numbers (eg. 1-100, 101-200, etc.) and each page has 20 entries, one for each piece of artwork. Thus an entry on line 15 of page 207 is given the identification number 207/15. Beginning with the third volume which starts in 1895, entries of unsold works from earlier volumes were transferred to unnumbered pages at the front of later volumes.
  Folders are arranged alphabetically by subject, then chronologically.
  - Catalog of Duplicate Prints, circa 1924-1926 (Box 69, Folder 18)
  - Frame Profile Book, circa 1885-1950 (Box 69, Folder 19)
  - Framed Print Stock Book, 1912, May (Box 69, Folder 20)
  - Framed Stock Book, circa 1919-1922 (Box 69, Folder 21)
  - Records of Works on Hand, Pages 1-90, 1881-1895 (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - Records of Works on Hand, Pages 100-200, 1886-1895 (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Records of Works on Hand, Pages 201-300, 1895-1903 (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Records of Works on Hand, Pages 301-400, 1903-1914 (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - Records of Works on Hand, Pages 401-500, 1914-1926 (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - Inventory Book, 1931, October 1 (Box BV113)
  - Inventory Book, 1932, October 1 (Box BV114)
  - Inventory Book, 1933, July 1 (Box BV115)
  - Inventory Book, 1934, July 1 (Box BV116)
  - Inventory Book, 1935, July 1 (Box BV117)
  - Inventory Book, 1936, July 1 (Box BV118)
  - Inventory Book, 1937, July 1 (Box BV119)
  - Inventory Book, 1940-1942, July 1 (Box BV120)
  - Inventory Book, 1950-1956, June 30 (Box BV121)
  - Print Stock Book (D), 1902-1907 (Box BV122)
  - Print Stock Book (E), 1907-1912 (Box BV123)
  - Print Stock Book (F), 1913-1917 (Box BV124)
  - Print Stock Book (G), 1918-1923 (Box BV125)
  - Print Stock Book (J), 1934-1945 (Box BV126)
  - Records of Works on Hand, Painting 5, 1926-1947 (Box BV127)
  - Records of Works on Hand, Artists, 1943-1969 (Box BV128)
- Printed Materials, circa 1880s-1968, bulk 1890s-1960s, Series 7:; (Boxes 70-75; 4.9 linear feet)
  An account of most of the exhibitions held at Doll & Richards from the 1880s-1968 can be created from the abundant exhibition announcements and catalogs. Found are six exhibition announcement and catalog books, disassembled and housed in folders in their original order of reverse chronological; loose exhibition announcements and catalogs; fragile clippings from newspapers; and a book, "William Stanley Haseltine," inscribed to Wendell Zoehler from Helen Haseltine Plowden. Many exhibition catalogs are annotated with notes and prices, and scattered price lists and notes can also be found here. Duplicate copies of announcements and catalogs have not been weeded.
  Folders are arranged alphabetically by subject, then chronologically by year range.
  - Book, William Stanley Haseltine by Helen Haseltine Plowden, 1947, 1953 (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - Exhibition Catalog and Announcement Book 1 [Disassembled], 1897-1915, (9 folders) (Box 70, Folder 7-15)
  - Exhibition Catalog and Announcement Book 2 [Disassembled], 1916-1924, (9 folders) (Box 71, Folder 1-9)
  - Exhibition Catalog and Announcement Book 3 [Disassembled], 1924-1933, (6 folders) (Box 71, Folder 10-16)
  - Exhibition Catalog and Announcement Book 4 [Disassembled], 1933-1945, (6 folders) (Box 71, Folder 17-22)
  - Exhibition Catalog and Announcement Book 5 [Disassembled], 1945-1952, (4 folders) (Box 72, Folder 1-4)
  - Exhibition Catalog and Announcement Book 6 [Disassembled], 1952-1959, (4 folders) (Box 72, Folder 5-8)
  - Exhibition Catalog and Announcement Book - Loose Materials, 1907, 1915-1916, 1953-1959 (Box 72, Folder 9)
  - Loose Exhibition Catalogs and Announcements [Photocopies], 1883-1899 (Box 72, Folder 10)
  - Loose Exhibition Catalogs and Announcements, 1890s (Box 72, Folder 11)
  - Loose Exhibition Catalogs and Announcements, 1891-1897 (Box 72, Folder 12)
  - Loose Exhibition Catalogs and Announcements, 1895-1908, (2 folders) (Box 72, Folder 13-14)
  - Loose Exhibition Catalogs and Announcements, 1896-1908 (Box 72, Folder 15)
  - Loose Exhibition Catalogs and Announcements, 1902-1908 (Box 72, Folder 16)
  - Loose Exhibition Catalogs and Announcements, 1908-1913, (2 folders) (Box 72, Folder 17-18)
  - Loose Exhibition Catalogs and Announcements, 1909-1916 (Box 72, Folder 19)
  - Loose Exhibition Catalogs and Announcements, 1912-1915 (Box 72, Folder 20)
  - Loose Exhibition Catalogs and Announcements, 1915-1919, (5 folders) (Box 73, Folder 1-5)
  - Loose Exhibition Catalogs and Announcements, 1915-1920 (Box 73, Folder 6)
  - Loose Exhibition Catalogs and Announcements, 1920-1924, (3 folders) (Box 73, Folder 7-9)
  - Loose Exhibition Catalogs and Announcements, 1925-1929, (3 folders) (Box 73, Folder 10-12)
  - Loose Exhibition Catalogs and Announcements, circa 1920s-1930s (Box 73, Folder 13)
  - Loose Exhibition Catalogs and Announcements, circa late 1920s-early 1930s (Box 73, Folder 14)
  - Loose Exhibition Catalogs and Announcements, circa 1920s-1940s (Box 73, Folder 15)
  - Loose Exhibition Catalogs and Announcements, 1930-1934, (3 folders) (Box 73, Folder 16-18)
  - Loose Exhibition Catalogs and Announcements, 1930-1934, (2 folders) (Box 74, Folder 1-2)
  - Loose Exhibition Catalogs and Announcements, 1935-1939, (4 folders) (Box 74, Folder 3-6)
  - Loose Exhibition Catalogs and Announcements, circa late 1930s-early 1940s (Box 74, Folder 7)
  - Loose Exhibition Catalogs and Announcements, 1940s (Box 74, Folder 8)
  - Loose Exhibition Catalogs and Announcements, 1940-1944, (2 folders) (Box 74, Folder 9-10)
  - Loose Exhibition Catalogs and Announcements, 1945-1949, (3 folders) (Box 74, Folder 11-13)
  - Loose Exhibition Catalogs and Announcements, circa 1940s-1950s (Box 74, Folder 14)
  - Loose Exhibition Catalogs and Announcements, 1950s (Box 74, Folder 15)
  - Loose Exhibition Catalogs and Announcements, 1950-1954, (2 folders) (Box 74, Folder 16-17)
  - Loose Exhibition Catalogs and Announcements, 1955-1959, (3 folders) (Box 74, Folder 18-20)
  - Loose Exhibition Catalogs and Announcements, circa 1950s-1960s (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - Loose Exhibition Catalogs and Announcements, 1960s (Box 75, Folder 2)
  - Loose Exhibition Catalogs and Announcements, 1960-1964, (2 folders) (Box 75, Folder 3-4)
  - Loose Exhibition Catalogs and Announcements, 1965-1968 (Box 75, Folder 5)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1908-1968 (Box 75, Folder 6)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1914, circa 1930-1941, 1963 (Box 75, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous Clippings, circa 1880s-1908 (Box 75, Folder 8)
- Photographs, circa 1880s-1960s, Series 8:; (Boxes 75-78; 2 linear feet)
  The black and white photographs of works of art chronicle the many artists with whom the gallery dealt. Also found are a few photographs of artists, including painter Jean-Pierre Alaux and sculptor Ethel Mundy in their studios; personal photographs of painter Ellice Endicott; travel photographs of painter A. Sheldon Pennoyer, and others. There are a handful of exhibition photographs which show works of art displayed in the gallery spaces at 2 Park Street, 71 Newbury Street and 138 Newbury Street. Scattered negatives, correspondence, inquiries from artists, artists' biographies, clippings, and other printed materials are also interspersed.
  Folders are arranged alphabetically by artist's last name or subject. Folder dates are based on the approximate date of the printing of the photograph.
  - A, circa 1920s-1961 (Box 75, Folder 9)
  - Abbott, Mary Ogden, 1932-1960 (Box 75, Folder 10)
  - Alaux, Jean-Pierre, circa 1940s-1958 (Box 75, Folder 11)
  - Artists, Miscellaneous, 1906, 1930s-1940s, 1957 (Box 75, Folder 12)
  - Augusta, George V., circa 1960s (Box 75, Folder 13)
  - B, 1918-circa 1960s (Box 75, Folder 14)
  - Batchelder, Jack, 1960s (Box 75, Folder 15)
  - Bellini, circa 1900s-1940s (Box 75, Folder 16)
  - Boston Art Club, 1883 (Box 75, Folder 17)
  - Browne, Margaret Fitzhugh, circa 1935-1938 (Box 75, Folder 18)
  - Bye, Ranulph, circa 1955 (Box 75, Folder 19)
  - C, circa 1920s-1950s (Box 75, Folder 20)
  - Charles, Sam, 1943-1950 (Box 75, Folder 21)
  - Coll-Bardolet, José, circa 1940s-1950s (Box 75, Folder 22)
  - Collier, Grace, circa 1950s-1960s (Box 75, Folder 23)
  - Copley, J.S., circa 1920s (Box 75, Folder 24)
  - Cresson, Margaret French - Exhibition (1937), circa 1937 (Box 75, Folder 25)
  - D, 1920s-1962 (Box 75, Folder 26)
  - D'Atri, Umberto, 1953 (Box 75, Folder 27)
  - de Botton, Jean, circa 1966 (Box 75, Folder 28)
  - Demetrios, George, circa 1949 (Box 75, Folder 29)
  - E, circa 1930s-1950s (Box 75, Folder 30)
  - Egginton, Frank, circa 1955-1956 (Box 75, Folder 31)
  - Ellery, Richard V., 1956 (Box 75, Folder 32)
  - Endicott, Ellice, circa 1943-1955 (Box 75, Folder 33)
  - Exhibition, Nippon-Kogei (Mar. 25 - Apr. 6, 1940), 1940 (Box 75, Folder 34)
  - Miscellaneous Exhibitions, 1908-1940 (Box 75, Folder 35)
  - F, circa 1930s-1950s (Box 75, Folder 36)
  - Franck, Frederick, 1958-1960 (Box 75, Folder 37)
  - G, circa 1930s-1950s (Box 75, Folder 38)
  - Gore, Ken, circa 1950s-1960s (Box 75, Folder 39)
  - H, circa 1940s-1950s (Box 75, Folder 40)
  - Hekking, William M., circa 1950s-1960s (Box 75, Folder 41)
  - Homburger, Freddy, 1957 (Box 75, Folder 42)
  - Homer, Winslow, circa 1920s-1950s (Box 75, Folder 43)
  - K, circa 1930s-1950s (Box 75, Folder 44)
  - Azeez Khayat Gallery - Objects, circa 1940s-1950s (Box 75, Folder 45)
  - Knox, Susan Ricker, 1937-1940s (Box 75, Folder 46)
  - L, circa 1910s-1950s (Box 75, Folder 47)
  - Logan, Robert Fulton, circa 1920s-1940s (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - Luce, Molly, 1967 (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - M, circa 1910s-1950s, (2 folders) (Box 76, Folder 3-4)
  - Manievich, Abraham, circa 1920s-1940s (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - McDonald, Mason, 1955 (Box 76, Folder 6)
  - McKenzie, R. Tait, 1911-1940s (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - Morris, Dudley, circa 1940s-1950s (Box 76, Folder 8)
  - Mundy, Ethel, circa 1930-1943 (Box 76, Folder 9)
  - N, circa 1920s-1961 (Box 76, Folder 10)
  - O, circa 1930s-1950s (Box 76, Folder 11)
  - Obata, Chiura, circa 1940s-1950s (Box 76, Folder 12)
  - O'Hara, Eliot, circa 1945-1963, (2 folders) (Box 76, Folder 13-14)
  - Orr, Mary Lincoln, circa 1940s-1950s (Box 76, Folder 15)
  - P, circa 1910s-1954 (Box 76, Folder 16)
  - Paine, L. Gerard, circa 1945-1956 (Box 76, Folder 17)
  - Parker, Kay Peterson, 1940, circa 1954-1957 (Box 76, Folder 18)
  - Patterson, Charles R., circa 1920s-1930s (Box 76, Folder 19)
  - Pavlosky, Vladimir, circa 1930s-1950s (Box 76, Folder 20)
  - Peale, Rembrandt, circa 1940 (Box 76, Folder 21)
  - Pennoyer, A. Sheldon, circa 1930s-1940s (Box 76, Folder 22)
  - Picasso, circa 1960s (Box 76, Folder 23)
  - Pleissner, Ogden M., circa 1930s-1950s (Box 76, Folder 24)
  - Poyer, Stan Pociecha, circa 1930s (Box 76, Folder 25)
  - Quinn, Edmond, circa 1900s-1920s (Box 76, Folder 26)
  - R, circa 1910s-1961 (Box 76, Folder 27)
  - Ripley, A. Lassel, circa 1940s-1950s (Box 76, Folder 28)
  - Rowland, Benjamin, 1940s-1950s (Box 76, Folder 29)
  - S, circa 1900s-1950s, (2 folders) (Box 76, Folder 30-31)
  - Scudder, Janet, 1918 (Box 76, Folder 32)
  - Shepler, Dwight, 1930s-1950s (Box 76, Folder 33)
  - Simone, Edgardo, circa 1910s (Box 76, Folder 34)
  - Smith, Joseph Lindon, circa 1940s-1950s (Box 76, Folder 35)
  - Spackman, Emily, circa 1900s-1920s (Box 76, Folder 36)
  - Steele, Marian Williams, circa 1940s-1960s (Box 76, Folder 37)
  - Stephenson, Benjamin T., 1940s-1950s (Box 76, Folder 38)
  - T, 1910s-1950s (Box 76, Folder 39)
  - Unidentified People, circa 1890s-1940s (Box 76, Folder 40)
  - V, circa 1920s-1940s (Box 76, Folder 41)
  - Vasileos, circa 1930s-1950s (Box 76, Folder 42)
  - W, circa 1910s-1960s (Box 76, Folder 43)
  - White, C. Scott, circa 1920s-1940s (Box 76, Folder 44)
  - Miscellaneous Works of Art, circa 1880s-1960s (Box 76, Folder 45)
  - Miscellaneous Works of Art, circa 1880s-1960s, (2 folders) (Box 77, Folder 1-2)
  - Wyeth, Andrew, 1930s-1950s (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - Y, circa 1910s-1930s (Box 77, Folder 4)
  - Zoluaga, circa 1930s-1960s (Box 77, Folder 5)
  - Cleveland Portraits by Alfred Jonniaux, circa 1900s-1920s, (13 items) (Box 78 (sol), Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous Works of Art, circa 1900s-1920s, (29 items) (Box 78 (sol), Folder 4)
- Scrapbooks, 1908-1968, bulk 1908-1943, Series 9:; (Boxes 77, 80; 1.1 linear feet)
  This series includes seven scrapbooks comprised of newspaper clippings and other printed materials related to Doll & Richards from 1909-1943. Also found is one scrapbook related to painter Ann Brockman of newspaper clippings, one pencil drawing, exhibition catalogs, and notices. The creators of the scrapbooks are unknown. All of the scrapbooks are very fragile and brittle.
  - Brockman, Ann, 1922-1945 (Box 77, Folder 6)
  - Doll & Richards Clippings Scrapbook, Cover, 1908-1915 (Box 77, Folder 7)
  - Doll & Richards Clippings Scrapbook, 1909-1915 (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - Doll & Richards Clippings Scrapbook, 1915-1917 (Box 77, Folder 9)
  - Doll & Richards Clippings Scrapbook, 1917-1920 (Box 77, Folder 10)
  - Doll & Richards Clippings Scrapbook, 1932-1936 (Box 77, Folder 11)
  - Doll & Richards Exhibitions Announcements Scrapbook, circa 1908-1928, 1931-1943 (Box 77, Folder 12)
  - Doll & Richards Exhibitions Announcements Scrapbook, 1964-1968 (Box 77, Folder 13)
  - Doll & Richards Clippings Scrapbook, 1920-1927, 1936-1937 (Box 80 (sol), Folder 1)
  - Doll & Richards Clippings Scrapbook, 1927-1932, 1936 (Box 80 (sol), Folder 2)
  - Doll & Richards Clippings Scrapbook, 1936-1943 (Box 80 (sol), Folder 3)